{
    "id": "6cf328b28d4a4ce288e98c1c27ce346c",
    "title": "Gap Filling Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He ……………………… a song at the party.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sang",
                "sing",
                "sung"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………… a letter yesterday.",
            "description": "The simple past is used with definite past time expressions. ",
            "answers": [
                "write",
                "written",
                "have written",
                "wrote"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Why don’t you ………………………… me?",
            "description": "Before an object, we use listen.",
            "answers": [
                "hear",
                "listen",
                "listen to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Always ………………………… the truth.",
            "description": "Speak is often used for one way communication.",
            "answers": [
                "say",
                "speak",
                "talk"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………………… to me since the last meeting.",
            "description": "The present perfect is used to talk about time up to now. ",
            "answers": [
                "did not speak",
                "does not speak",
                "has not spoken"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "They ……………………….. the whole matter.",
            "description": "Discuss is one of those verbs that are not followed by a preposition. ",
            "answers": [
                "discussed",
                "discussed about",
                "discussed on"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He lost the watch shortly after he …………………………. it.",
            "description": "The simple past and present perfect are possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "bought",
                "has bought",
                "had bought"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We ………………………. tennis every day.",
            "description": "The simple present is used to talk about routines and habits. ",
            "answers": [
                "play",
                "are playing",
                "plays"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The quality of the mangoes we bought …………………………… not good.",
            "description": "Here the subject is the singular noun quality. ",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "One of my sisters …………………………. abroad.",
            "description": "Here the subject is the singular expression one. ",
            "answers": [
                "live",
                "lives",
                "are living"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither of them …………………………. here at the moment.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after neither and either. ",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "More than one …………………………… absent today.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "student is",
                "students are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}